Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook [5], "Clippings of interest", 1901-1925; related to Street & Smith publications from the general press (Oversize 5)
  - Scrapbook [6], 1915-1949; clippings, mostly related to Street & Smith publications and authors (Oversize 6)
  - Scrapbook [7], 1896-1941; mostly relating to other publishers, competitors (Oversize 7)
- Scripts
  - The Avenger
    - Episodes, by number, 1941; undated (Box 285)
      no. 1 High-Tide Murders, 23pp; includes list of characters
      no. 2 Mystery of the Giant Brain, 23 pp; includes list of characters and actors
      no. 3 Rendezvous with Murder, 21 pp.
      no. 4 Eyes of Shiva, 22 pp.
      no. 5 Coins of Death, 21 pp.
      no. 6 Mystery of Dead Man's Rock, 20 pp.
      no. 7 Tunnel of Disaster, 21 pp.
      no. 8 Crypt of Thoth, 20 pp.
      no. 9 Melody of Murder, 19 pp.
      no. 10 Fiery Deaths, 20 pp.
      no. 11 Ghost Murder, 22 pp.
      no. 12 Blue Pearls, 21 pp.
      no. 13 Wingate Heirs, 19 pp.
      no. 14 Thoroughbred Murder, 20 pp.
      no. 15 Department of Death, 20 pp.
      no. 16 Keys to the City, 21 pp.
      no. 17 Death in Mid-Air, 20 pp.
      no. 18 Hooded Circle, 20 pp.
      no. 19 Death Rings the Bell, 21 pp.
      no. 20 Subway Ghost, 20 pp.
      no. 21 Cradle of Doom, 20 pp.
      no. 22 Death Meets the Boat, 19 pp.
      no. 23 Murder Hits the Jackpot, 19 pp.
      no. 24 Diploma of Death, 18 pp.
      no. 25 Shot in the Dark, 19 pp.
      no. 26 Death Counts Ten, 20 pp.
      [no number] Hate Master (Field Operators and Inner Circle of Justice, Inc.; Avenger not named), 25 Jul 1941, 21 pp.
      [no number] Tear Drop Tank (Inner Circle of Justice, Inc.; Avenger not named), 1 Aug 1941, 22 pp.
      [no number] River of Ice (Justice, Inc.; Avenger not named), 15 Aug 1941, 22 pp.
      [no number] Three Gold Crowns (character of Benson opens script with "Quietly with deadly incisiveness! Enemies of Justice! This is the Avenger!" Later: character is referred to as Richard Benson, Chief of Justice, Inc.), 22 Aug 1941, 24 pp.
      [no number] Blood Ring, 29 Aug 1941, 20 pp.
      [no number] Devil's Horns, 2 Sep 1941, 21 pp.
      [no number] Avenger, 9 Sep 1941, 20 pp.
  - Chick Carter
    - no. 1 Chick Carter-Boy Detective, 4 Jul 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 2 Chick Carter-Boy Detective, 5 Jul 1943; 12 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 3 Chick Carter-Boy Detective, 6 Jul 1943; 13 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 4 Major Pennington's Life & Death Decision, 7 Jul 1943; 12 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 5 Showdown in Crystal Cave, 8 Jul 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 6 When Tables Turn, 11 Jul 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 7 Echoes of Death, 12 Jul 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 8 The Bubbling Pool, 13 Jul 1943; 13 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 9 No Escape, 14 Jul 1943; title page only - no script; typed note: "Only 1 copy of no. 9 script received from Mr. deGrouchy's office. Therefore sent that copy to the register of copyrights."; 13 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 10 Big Surprise, 15 Jul 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 11 Action on the Bridge, 19 Jul 1943; 13 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 12 Death from the Dark, 20 Jul 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 13 The Rattler Makes Plans, 21 Jul 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 14 Chick & Sue Play a Lone Hand, 22 Jul 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 15 Roaring Death, 23 Jul 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 16 Chick Carter Thinks Fast, 26 Jul 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 17 Chick Carter Takes a Bold Step, 27 Jul 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 18 Out of the Wreck, 28 Jul 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 19 Book of Evidence Revealed, 29 Jul 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 20 The Rattler's Fury, 30 Jul 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 21 The Chase, 2 Aug 1943; 13 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 22 The Blockade, 3 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 23 The Roundup, 4 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 24 High Speed, 5 Aug 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 25 Action on Number 30 West-bound Freight Express, 6 Aug 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 26 The Answer to the Mystery, 9 Aug 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 27 Marked for Death, 10 Aug 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 28 The Fire!, 11 Aug 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 29 Silas Grimm Plays his Trump Card!, 12 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 30 Jail Break!, 13 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 31 A Clue!, 16 Aug 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 32 Trapped, 17 Aug 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 33 Daring Escape!, 18 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 34 Rendezvous at Willow Tree Glen!, 19 Aug 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 35 The Vanishing Trucks, 20 Aug 1943; 13 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 36 X24- The Rattler's Emergency Order, 23 Aug 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 37 The Mayor's Final Decision, 24 Aug 1943; 14 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 38 Death Strikes in Crystal Cave, 25 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 39 Death Around the Bend, 26 Aug 1943; 15 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 40 The Trial of Blood, 27 Aug 1943; 17 pp. (Box 286)
    - no. 41 The Mystery of the Caverns, 30 Aug 1943; 16 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 42 Escape!, 31 Aug 1943; 16 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 43 Cheating Certain Death, 1 Sep 1943; 16 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 44 A Race with Fire, 2 Sep 1943; 18 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 45 untitled, 3 Sep 1943; 15 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 46 The Seconds before the Crash, 6 Sep 1943; 17 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 47 The Rattler's Plan, 7 Sep 1943; 17 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 48 The Cave In, 8 Sep 1943; 17 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 49 Below the Earth's Surface, 9 Sep 1943; 18 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 50 Chief Barlow's Reserve, 10 Sep 1943; 18 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 51 A Deal in Death, 13 Sep 1943; 18 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 52 Death by Degrees, 14 Sep 1943; 17 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 53 Chief Barlow's Crisis!, 15 Sep 1943; 19 pp. (Box 287)
    - no. 54 The Warning, 16 Sep 1943; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 55 The Rattler and the Life Line of Oil, 17 Sep 1943; includes inter office memorandum stating episodes 55 and 56 will have the same title); 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 56 The Rattler and the Life Line of Oil, 20 Sep 1943; same title as No. 55 but different episode; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 57 The Flood, 21 Sep 1943; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 58 Chick's Plan, 22 Sep 1943; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 59 untitled, 23 Sep 1943; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 60 untitled, 24 Sep 1943; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 61 untitled, 27 Sep 1943; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 62 untitled, 28 Sep 1943; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 63 untitled, 29 Sep 1943; 14 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 64 untitled, 30 Sep 1943; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 287)
    - no. 65 untitled, 1 Oct 1943; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 288)
    - no. 66 untitled, 4 Oct 1943; 17 pp.; 2 copies (Box 288)
    - no. 67 untitled, 5 Oct 1943; each has an additional 3 page substitute closing for the last scene; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 288)
    - no. 68 untitled, 6 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 69 untitled, 7 Oct 1943; 16 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 70 untitled, 8 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 71 untitled, 11 Oct 1943; 16 pp.; 2 copies (Box 288)
    - no. 72 untitled, 12 Oct 1943; 17 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 73 untitled, 13 Oct 1943; 16 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 74 untitled, 14 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 75 untitled, 15 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 76 untitled, 18 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 77 untitled, 19 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 78 untitled, 20 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 79 untitled, 21 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 80 untitled, 22 Oct 1943; 14 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 81 untitled, 25 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 82 untitled, 26 Oct 1943; 14 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 83 untitled, 27 Oct 1943; 14 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 84 untitled, 28 Oct 1943; 14 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 85 untitled, 29 Oct 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 86 untitled, 1 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 87 untitled, 2 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 88 untitled, 3 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 89 untitled, 4 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 90 untitled, 5 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 91 untitled, 8 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 92 untitled, 9 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 93 untitled, 10 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 94 untitled, 11 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 288)
    - no. 95 untitled, 12 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 96 untitled, 15 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 97 untitled, 16 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 98 untitled, 17 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 99 untitled, 18 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 100 untitled, 19 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 101 untitled, 22 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 102 untitled, 23 Nov 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 103 untitled, 24 Nov 1943; 16 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 104 untitled, 25 Nov 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 105 untitled, 26 Nov 1943; 16 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 106 untitled, 29 Nov 1943; 16 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 107 untitled, 30 Nov 1943; 17 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 108 untitled, 1 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 109 untitled, 2 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 110 untitled, 3 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 111 untitled, 6 Dec 1943; 16 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 112 untitled, 7 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 113 untitled, 8 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 114 untitled, 9 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 115 untitled, 10 Dec 1943; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 289)
    - no. 116 untitled, 13 Dec 1943; 10 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 117 untitled, 14 Dec 1943; 11 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 118 untitled, 15 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 119 untitled, 16 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 120 untitled, 17 Dec 1943; 16 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 121 untitled, 20 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 122 untitled, 21 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 123 untitled, 22 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 124 untitled, 23 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 125 untitled, 24 Dec 1943; 11 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 126 untitled, 27 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 127 untitled, 28 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 128 untitled, 29 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 289)
    - no. 129 untitled, 30 Dec 1943; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 130 untitled, 31 Dec 1943; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 131 untitled, 3 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 132 untitled, 4 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 133 untitled, 5 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 134 untitled, 6 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 135 untitled, 7 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 136 untitled, 10 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 137 untitled, 11 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 138 untitled, 12 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 139 untitled, 13 Jan 1944; 14 pp.; 2 copies (Box 290)
    - no. 140 untitled, 14 Jan 1944; 14 pp.; 2 copies (Box 290)
    - no. 141 untitled, 17 Jan 1944; 15 pp.; 2 copies (Box 290)
    - no. 142 untitled, 18 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 143 untitled, 19 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 144 untitled, 20 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 145 untitled, 21 Jan 1944; 14 pp.; 2 copies (Box 290)
    - no. 146 untitled, 24 Jan 1944; 16 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 147 untitled, 25 Jan 1944; 14 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 148 untitled, 26 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 149 untitled, 27 Jan 1944; 17 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 150 untitled, 28 Jan 1944; 16 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 151 untitled, 31 Jan 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 152 untitled, 1 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 153 untitled, 2 Feb 1944; 16 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 154 untitled, 3 Feb 1944; 16 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 155 untitled, 4 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 156 untitled, 7 Feb 1944; 16 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 157 untitled, 8 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 158 untitled, 9 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 159 untitled, 10 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 160 untitled, 11 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 161 untitled, 14 Feb 1944; 16 pp. (Box 290)
    - no. 162 untitled, 15 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 163 untitled, 16 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 164 untitled, 17 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 165 untitled, 18 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 166 untitled, 21 Feb 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 167 untitled, 22 Feb 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 168 untitled, 23 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 169 untitled, 24 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 170 untitled, 25 Feb 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 171 untitled, 28 Feb 1944; 13 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 172 untitled, 29 Feb 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 173 untitled, 1 Mar 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 174 untitled, 2 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 175 untitled, 3 Mar 1944; 16 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 176 untitled, 6 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 177 untitled, 7 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 178 untitled, 8 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 179 untitled, 9 Mar 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 180 untitled, 10 Mar 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 181 untitled, 13 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 182 untitled, 14 Mar 1944; 13 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 183 untitled, 15 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 184 untitled, 16 Mar 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 185 untitled, 17 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 186 untitled, 20 Mar 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 187 untitled, 21 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 188 untitled, 22 Mar 1944; 12 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 189 untitled, 23 Mar 1944; 12 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 190 untitled, 24 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 191 untitled, 27 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 192 untitled, 28 Mar 1944; 16 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 193 untitled, 29 Mar 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 194 untitled, 30 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 195 untitled, 31 Mar 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 196 untitled, 3 Apr 1944; 14 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 197 untitled, 4 Apr 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 198 untitled, 5 Apr 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 199 untitled, 6 Apr 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 200 untitled, 7 Apr 1944; 15 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 201 untitled, 10 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 291)
    - no. 202 untitled, 11 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 203 untitled, 12 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 204 untitled, 13 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 205 untitled, 14 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 206 untitled, 17 Apr 1944; 17 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 207 untitled, 18 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 208 untitled, 19 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 209 untitled, 20 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 210 untitled, 21 Apr 1944; 17 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 211 untitled, 24 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 212 untitled, 25 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 213 untitled, 26 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 214 untitled, 27 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 215 untitled, 28 Apr 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 216 untitled, 1 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 217 untitled, 2 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 218 untitled, 3 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 219 untitled, 4 May 1944; 15 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 220 untitled, 5 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 221 untitled, 8 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 222 untitled, 9 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 223 untitled, 10 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 224 untitled, 11 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 225 untitled, 12 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 226 untitled, 15 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 227 untitled, 16 May 1944; 17 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 228 untitled, 17 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 229 untitled, 18 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 230 untitled, 19 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 231 untitled, 22 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 232 untitled, 23 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 233 untitled, 24 May 1944; 13 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 234 untitled, 25 May 1944; 13 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 235 untitled, 26 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 236 untitled, 29 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 237 untitled, 30 May 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 238 untitled, 31 May 1944; 14 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 239 untitled, 1 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 292)
    - no. 240 untitled, 2 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 241 untitled, 5 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 242 untitled, 6 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 243 untitled, 7 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 244 untitled, 8 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 245 untitled, 9 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 246 untitled, 12 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 247 untitled, 13 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 248 untitled, 14 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 249 untitled, 15 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 250 untitled, 16 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 251 untitled, 19 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 252 untitled, 20 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 253 untitled, 21 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 254 untitled, 22 Jun 1944; 17 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 255 untitled, 23 Jun 1944; 17 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 256 untitled, 24 Jun 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 257 untitled, 27 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 258 untitled, 28 Jun 1944; 17 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 259 untitled, 29 Jun 1944; 17 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 260 untitled, 30 Jun 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 261 untitled, 3 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 262 untitled, 4 Jul 1944; 10 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 263 untitled, 5 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 264 untitled, 6 Jul 1944; 17 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 265 untitled, 7 Jul 1944; 17 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 266-267 untitled, 11 Jul 1944; includes note saying that due to the Republican Convention on July 10th, there was no script for that day; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 268 untitled, 12 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 269 untitled, 13 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 270 untitled, 14 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 271 untitled, 17 Jul 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 272 untitled, 18 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 273 untitled, 19 Jul 1944; 15 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 274 untitled, 20 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 275 untitled, 21 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 276 untitled, 24 Jul 1944; 16 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 277 untitled, 25 Jul 1944; 10 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 278 untitled, 26 Jul 1944; 8 pp. (Box 293)
    - no. 279 untitled, 27 Jul 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 280 untitled, 28 Jul 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 281-282 untitled, 1 Aug 1944; includes note saying that due to the Democratic Convention on July 31th, Chick Carter was off the air for that day; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 283 untitled, 2 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 284 untitled, 3 Aug 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 285 untitled, 4 Aug 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 286 untitled, 7 Aug 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 287 untitled, 8 Aug 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 288 untitled, 9 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 289 untitled, 10 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 290 untitled, 11 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 291 untitled, 14 Aug 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 292 untitled, 15 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 293 untitled, 16 Aug 1944; 16 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 294 untitled, 17 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 295 untitled, 18 Aug 1944; 16 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 296 untitled, 21 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 297 untitled, 22 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 298 untitled, 23 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 299 untitled, 24 Aug 1944; 16 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 300 untitled, 25 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 301 untitled, 28 Aug 1944; 16 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 302 untitled, 29 Aug 1944; 17 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 303 untitled, 30 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 304 untitled, 31 Aug 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 305 untitled, 1 Sep 1944; "Corrected" copy; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 306 untitled, 4 Sep 1944; 16 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 307 untitled, 5 Sep 1944; "Revised version"; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 308 untitled, 6 Sep 1944; "Revised version"; 13 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 309 untitled, 7 Sep 1944; "Revised version"; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 310 untitled, 8 Sep 1944; "Revised version"; 13 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 311 untitled, 11 Sep 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 312 untitled, 12 Sep 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 313 untitled, 13 Sep 1944; 10 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 314 untitled, 14 Sep 1944; 10 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 315 untitled, 15 Sep 1944; 13 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 316 untitled, 18 Sep 1944; 14 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 317 untitled, 19 Sep 1944; 15 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 318 untitled, 20 Sep 1944; 13 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 319 untitled, 21 Sep 1944; 12 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 320 untitled, 22 Sep 1944; 12 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 321 untitled, 25 Sep 1944; 12 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 322 untitled, 26 Sep 1944; 12 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 323 untitled, 27 Sep 1944; 12 pp. (Box 294)
    - no. 324 untitled, 28 Sep 1944; 13 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 325 untitled, 29 Sep 1944; 14 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 326 untitled, 2 Oct 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 327 untitled, 3 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 328 untitled, 4 Oct 1944; 14 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 329 untitled, 5 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 330 untitled, 6 Oct 1944; 14 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 331 untitled, 9 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 332 untitled, 10 Oct 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 333 untitled, 11 Oct 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 334 untitled, 12 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 335 untitled, 13 Oct 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 336 untitled, 16 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 337 untitled, 17 Oct 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 338 untitled, 18 Oct 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 339 untitled, 19 Oct 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 340 untitled, 20 Oct 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 341 untitled, 23 Oct 1944; 18 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 342 untitled, 24 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 343 untitled, 25 Oct 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 344 untitled, 26 Oct 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 345 untitled, 27 Oct 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 346 untitled, 30 Oct 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 347 untitled, 31 Oct 1944; 14 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 348 untitled, 1 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 349 untitled, 2 Nov 1944; 14 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 350 untitled, 3 Nov 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 351 untitled, 6 Nov 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 352 untitled, 7 Nov 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 353 untitled, 8 Nov 1944; 17 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 354 untitled, 9 Nov 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 355 untitled, 10 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 356 untitled, 13 Nov 1944; 9 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 357 untitled, 14 Nov 1944; 9 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 358 untitled, 15 Nov 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 359 untitled, 16 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 360 untitled, 17 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 361 untitled, 20 Nov 1944; 14 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 362 untitled, 21 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 363 untitled, 22 Nov 1944; 15 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 364 untitled, 23 Nov 1944; 12 pp. (Box 295)
    - no. 365 untitled, 24 Nov 1944; 14 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 366 untitled, 27 Nov 1944; 14 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 367 untitled, 28 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 368 untitled, 29 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 369 untitled, 30 Nov 1944; 16 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 370 untitled, 1 Dec 1944; 17 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 371 untitled, 4 Dec 1944; 19 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 372 untitled, 5 Dec 1944; 17 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 373 untitled, 6 Dec 1944; 18 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 374 untitled, 7 Dec 1944; 17 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 375 untitled, 8 Dec 1944; 17 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 376 untitled, 11 Dec 1944; 16 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 377 untitled, 12 Dec 1944; 15 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 378 untitled, 13 Dec 1944; 17 pp. (Box 296)
    - no. 379 untitled, 14 Dec 1944; 17 pp. (Box 296)